I sell Botox, filler hormones, peptides, and weight management.
We do $6.7 million in revenue a year.
What lever do we need to pull next?
Is it operations?
Is it people?
Is it this?
Is it that?
Then what stops you from getting from three to five?
I think proving out this next model is the key to it of knowing, getting it booked.
What's profit?
About 15%.
It's a little low.
I'm guessing the first one had better margins than the second and the third.
They did.
This happens for literally everyone, so don't worry about it.
Start One works really well.
You guys are both in the business.
Founder Magic, amazing.
You say, hey, wouldn't it be cool if we just did twice as much money?
You're like, yes, let's do it.
You open up the second location, split attention.
This one comes up not as high as the first one.
This one comes down a little bit because you guys aren't there, but that almost all came
from the bottom line.
Now you're like, wait, so now I have twice the liability, but I'm almost making the same
amount of money as I had with just one, but now I have two.
Then you're like, okay, but that's our new baseline.
We open our third one, then we'll still get our at least a 50% improvement.
What happens is this one actually never really got the full lift as you wanted, but you picked
your location better here because you thought a little bit more about it.
You got your square footage a little bit more tight, and you knew the few services you're
going to do.
Then you do that, and this one's a little bit more profitable, but it's way smaller
top line because you haven't really jammed it as much.
You overexpanded.
Why don't we fix the current ones and get those to 35 or 40 and then do the fourth one
once we've fixed the current ones.